http://www.fungi.com/pages/privacy-policy

Indoor
Where Did Our Indoor Kits Go?
Indoor
Where Did Our Indoor Kits Go?
Contact Us
Contact us if you have questions about our privacy policies. You can e-mail us at info@fungi.com, you can call us at 800-780-9126 or you can contact us at our mailing address:Fungi Perfecti, LLCPO Box 7634Olympia, WA 98507USA
Internet Privacy:
Data CollectionWe collect three different types of data: non-identifiable basic information, non-identifiable cookies, and information (name, email, phone number, company) that you choose to give us through filling out our “Contact Us,” “Submit a Recipe” or “Email Newsletter” forms.
We Collect Non-Identifiable Basic InformationWe collect click-stream data, HTTP protocol elements, and search terms. We use these data for research and development, system tracking, and helping visitors reach the right page. These data are non-identifiable. This means we can’t (and have no interest in trying to) identify any individual person via these data. We also collect access logs and search strings. We use these data to help improve our site.We Collect Non-Identifiable Cookie InformationWe collect HTTP cookie data. Again, we use these data for research and development, system tracking, and helping visitors reach the right page. Our cookies are non-identifiable, meaning we can’t (and don’t want to) identify you or any individual person via these data. We collect these cookie data to help improve our web site.
What Are "Cookies"?A cookie is a piece of information sent to a browser by a web server. The browser then returns that information to the Web server. This is how some Web pages “remember” your previous visits; for example, an e-commerce site might use a cookie to remember which items you’ve placed in your online shopping cart. Cookies can also store user preference information, log-in data, etc. Cookies let sites provide you with tailored information.Links To Other SitesOur sites link to and redirect to third-party websites. We’re not responsible for the privacy practices or the content on those sites. When you leave our site, it is wise to check the privacy policy of the site you reach. Those sites might place their own cookies, collect data, and use personal information in different ways than we do.The privacy policy described on this page only applies to our sites.SecurityWe have security measures in place to protect the information we collect. We use strong encryption to keep these data safe from loss, tampering, misuse, and unauthorized access.Policy ChangesShould we modify our privacy policy, we’ll update this page accordingly. If we make changes to our policy, we’ll treat previously collected data in accordance with our policy in effect when the data were collected.Acceptance Of This Privacy PolicyBy using this site, you’re indicating you’ve read and accept our privacy policy. If you don’t agree with this policy, please do not use our site. Continuing to use of this site after we post changes to these terms means you accept those changes. If you do not accept these terms but would like to place an order or request information, please feel free to contact us via phone at 800-780-9126 or 360-426-9292. Thank you!
Mail Privacy:
Fungi Perfecti does not sell, rent or otherwise distribute mailing information for our customers to any other parties.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding our mail privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.
Explore
Shop All Collections
Articles & Information
About Us
Careers at Fungi Perfecti / Host Defense
Events
Support
Company Policies
Information & Updates
Holiday Shipping Schedule
Contact Us
Login
Join Our Community
Sign up for Fungi Perfecti Company and Product updates.
Subscribe
Follow us
Find us on Facebook
Find us on Instagram
Find us on Youtube
Fungi Perfecti
©2018 Fungi Perfecti LLCPO Box 7634Olympia, WA 98507USA Order Toll Free (US & Canada): 800-780-9126Phone: 360-426-9292Email: info@fungi.com
Company Policies
Information & Updates
Holiday Shipping Schedule
Contact Us
Login
Copyright © 2020 Fungi Perfecti.
Empire Theme by Pixel Union. Powered by Shopify
*These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease.
Added to your cart:
Subtotal
